

# Technical Skills and Competences

# Substantial Technical Literacy

Affinity towards modules and systems optimisation

# Decent Software Products and Systems Knowledge

Operating Systems, Graphic interfaces, Microsoft Office

Multimedia processing

## Content Management Systems

WordPress: DBMS

#### **Hardware Components**

Constructive modules, computer peripherals

#### **Local Area Networks**

✓ Building, configuring, optimisation and support of Local Computer Networks, posts, clients and servers

# Social Skills & Competences

Building, managing and motivating teams devoted to marketing research and new products introduction

Acquired in Condor
Commerce Ltd. and Condor
Design Ltd, Sofia 1994-1996
during the years of my
Higher Education

### VELIN **SKENDEROV**

Applicant for UniCredit Bulbank Corporate Banking Associate, Large, Burgas

### **Profile**

A qualified steady individual with strong interpersonal entrepreneurial skills, prone to bring the appropriate face to a business by delivering premium class customer service. Could offer creative think-ing outside of the box, within a team or individually, to the utmost satisfaction of relevant stakeholders, in line with the market realities and competitive strategy followed by **UniCredit Bulbank** to mutual benefit of all parties concerned. Being well experienced in retail and information technology sectors, I consider myself properly suited to provide outstanding Corporate Banking Associate services in Burgas as a member of first rate financial institution.

### Experience

2014 - 2020 Bus

**Business Management Systems Ltd, Customer Relationships Department** 

Customer Support Specialist, Bourgas.

Description of the job position and esponsibilities

2012 - 2013

Infrastructure Technology Services and Engineering Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Quality Support Department

Receiving Orders Technologist, Bourgas. Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2011 - 2012

LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Organisational Support Group

Receiving Orders Leading Technologist, Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2008 - 2011

LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Information Technologies Organisational Support Group

Specialist/Information Technologies Operational Support , Bourgas.

# Organisational Skills and Competences

#### Marketing

✓ Sales of goods (mass products) and services

### Introduction to the market

Services, Information
 Products and Technologies induction

### General

## Interdisciplinary interests

✓ general knowledge;

Shotokan Katate and Judo practice

### **Driving License**

Category B

### Disposable Referent Documents

#### Letter of Recommendation

from Business Management Systems Ltd Managing Director (last employer) /look here/

#### **Business English Certificate**

✓ Cambridge B2 Vantage /look <u>here</u>/

#### **Document Doctoral Course**

 Bulgarian Academy of Science, Central Laboratory of Biomedical Engineering /look here/

#### Certificate

✓ Design and Programming Support of Distributed Control System MIC /look here/

## Master's Level Qualification Degree Certificate

University of National and World Economy, Sofia /look <a href="here">here</a> /

2005 - 2008

LUKOIL Technology Services Bulgaria Ltd, Information Technologies Administration, Program Technologies and Databases Department

Programmer, Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities.

2002 - 2005

LUKOIL Neftochim Burgas AD, Information Computing Center, Cash Accounts Balance Department

Programmer, Bourgas.

Description of the job, position and responsibilities

**2001 - 2002** 

# KRS Iliya Iliev Sole Proprietorship Company, Yambol

Trade, import and distribution of radio-electronic equipment, black & white household appliances, mobile communication, Bourgas.
Customer Support Specialist

Description of the job, position and responsibilities

#### Education

**2008 - 2009** 

**Business English** 

Foreign Languages and Management Centre, Bourgas Cambridge English: Business Certificates (BEC) B2 Business Vantage Certificate

2007 - 2007

Intuitional Fuzzy Sets - Theory and Application

Bulgarian Academy of Science, BME, Sofia Doctoral Course "Theory and Application of Intuitional Fuzzy Sets"

2001 - 2001

Design and Software Support of Disributed System MIC

MICONT Ltd, Sofia

Design and Software Support of Distributed System MIC for Control of Technological Plants in Real Time

1989 - 1999

**Higher Education** 

University of National and World Economy, Sofia Industrial Management Master

1984 - 1989

**Secondary Education** 

High School of Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas Information Computing Machines Operator/Programmer Certificate

#### **Higher Education Diploma**

University of National and World Economy, Sofia /look here/

# Secondary Education Diploma

✓ High School of Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas /look here up/

Certificate of acquired professional qualification Programmer of Computer Equipment High School of

- ✓ Natural Sciences and Mathematics "Academician Nikola Obreshkov", Bourgas /look <u>here</u> down/
- Medical Disability Commission | Certificate /look here/

### **Contact**

- ♠ Bourgas
- **4** +359 56 825333
- **1** +359 88 8470027
- Velin.Skenderoff@gmail.com

### Foreign Languages

#### Russian

Reading Writing Speaking



#### **English**

Reading Writing Speaking

